Henry F. Dobyns Papers 1732-2009 (bulk 1950-2000)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series IV: Gila River Indian Community Files, 1732-2004
  - Subseries 3: Case and Research Files, 1732-2003
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1990 (Box 89, Folder 10-11)
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1991 (Box 89, Folder 12-14)
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1991 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1992 (Box 90, Folder 2-5)
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1993 (Box 90, Folder 6-8)
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1994 (Box 90, Folder 9-13)
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1995 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Globe Equity 59- Pleadings, 1999-2001 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Globe Equity 59: Report on Estimate of Gila River losses between Coolidge Dam to Ashurst- Hayden Diversion Dam/China Wash, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Globe Equity 59- Rules Committee, 1992-1994 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Globe Equity 59- Settlement meeting transcripts, 1994 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Globe Equity 59- Transcripts, 1930 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts February 12, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts February 13, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts February 14, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts February 15, 1990 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts November 12, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts November 13, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts November 14, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts November 18, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts November 19, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts November 20, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts November 21, 1991 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts May 11, 1993 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts May 12, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial Transcripts May 13, 1993 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial transcripts November 7-10, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Globe Equity 59- Trial transcripts November 11-17, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Goldman, Fred- The Relationship of Ground Water to Surface Water, 1987 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Gookin Engineers- Call System- Pooling Provisions, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Gookin Engineers- Call System report, 1998 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Gookin Engineers- GRIR San Carlos Indian Irrigation Project- Supplemental Wells Necessity and Justification, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Gookin Engineers- Hydrologic Context of Gila River Decree, undated (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - Gookin Engineers- Hydrologic History of the Gila River Indian Reservation, 1999 (Box 92, Folder 10-11)
    - Gookin Engineers- Hydrologic Studies of Gila, Salt and Santa Cruz Rivers prepared for Bureau of Indian Affairs, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - Gookin Engineers memos, 1982 (Box 92, Folder 13-14)
    - Gookin Engineers memos, 1983-1991 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Gookin Engineers- Pomerene Water Association Water Requirements, 1994 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Gookin Engineers- Pumping and the Globe Equity 59 Decree, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Gookin Engineers- Pumping and Globe Equity No. 59 Witness Report, 2001 (Box 92, Folder 18-19)
    - Gookin Engineers- Rebuttal of Pumping and the Globe Equity 59 Decree, 2002 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - Gookin Engineers research materials, 1995, 1999 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Gookin Engineers- A Report concerning Counts I, II, III, IV Globe Equity 59, 1990 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Gookin Engineers- A Report concerning Counts Nine, Ten, Eleven and Twelve Globe Equity 59, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Gookin Engineers- A Report concerning Counts IX, X, XI and XII Globe Equity No. 59, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Gookin Engineers- Seepage and Transit Loss Deductions from Apportionments, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Gookin Engineers- Technical Report on the Connection of Surface Water and Groundwater, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Gookin Engineers- Technical Report on Various Aspects of Globe Equity 59, 1994 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Hackenberg, Robert- Ecological Change and Economic Adjustment on the Gila River Indian Reservatio,., 1974 (Box 93, Folder 8-9)
    - Halderman, Allan- Irrigation Water Requirements Silver Creek Watershed, Arizona, 1992 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Halpenny, Leonard- Groundwater and Surface water Interconnection in Arizona, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Halpenny, Leonard- Interrelations between Groundwater and Surface water within the Buckeye Water Conservation and Drainage District, 1987 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Hearing documents, undated (Box 93, Folder 13-14)
    - The Heritage Writing Project, 1988 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Hill v Herrick, 1889 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Hydro- Analysis- Hydrology of Safford Valley, 1991 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Index to Arizona news in Arizona Daily Star, 1954 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Index of documents forwarded to Dobyns, 1994 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Indexes, 1992-1994 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Indian Finance Digest, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Indian Office circulars, 1854-1878 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - An Indian Quest for Justice, 1984 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1935 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1936 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1937 (Box 94, Folder 9-12)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1938 (Box 94, Folder 13-14)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1939 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1940 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1941-1943 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1944-1947 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1948-1978 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1981-1989 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - In Equity No. E 59- Globe, 1990 (Box 95, Folder 2-3)
    - Information sources, 1825, 1833 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Information sources, 1846 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Information sources, 1849 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Information sources, 1854-1859 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Information sources, 1860-1863 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Information sources, 1864-1867 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Information sources, 1869 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Information sources, 1881-1899 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Information sources, 1901 (Box 95, Folder 12)
    - Information sources, 1902 (Box 95, Folder 13)
    - Information sources, 1903 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    - Information sources, 1904 (Box 95, Folder 15)
    - Information sources, 1905 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Information sources, 1906-1907 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Information sources, 1910 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Information sources, 1911 (Box 96, Folder 4-5)
    - Information sources, 1912-1913 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Information sources, 1914 (Box 96, Folder 7-9)
    - Information sources, 1915-1917 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Information sources, 1920-1926 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Information sources, 1927 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - Information sources, 1928-1929 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - Information sources, 1931-1933 (Box 96, Folder 14)
    - Information sources, 1932 (Box 96, Folder 15)
    - Information sources, 1934-1935 (Box 96, Folder 16)
    - Information sources, 1936 (Box 96, Folder 17)
    - Information sources, 1937-1938 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Information sources, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 2-3)
    - Information sources, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Information sources, 1942 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Information sources, 1943-1945 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Information sources, 1950 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Information sources, 1954 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Information sources, 1955 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Information sources, 1956-1957 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Information sources, 1961-1972 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Information sources, undated (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Information sources- GRIC history, 1913 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Information sources- Gileños, 1846-1904 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Information sources- Globe Equity 59, 1925-1928 (Box 97, Folder 15-16)
    - Information sources- Globe Equity 59, 1934-1935 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Information sources- History of the Pima- Maricopa Confederation, 1732, 1842-1843 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Information sources- History of the Pima- Maricopa Confederation, 1900-1913 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Interview- Rhodes, William, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Interview- Sunn, Nick, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Kennecott Copper Corporation, 1977-1979 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Kent Decree, 1910 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Kohlhoff, Karl- Expert report, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Kollenborn, Henry- Report on Water Supply and Water Use for the San Carlos Irrigation Project, 1943 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Kraeger- Rovey, Catherine- Preliminary Report: Hydrologic Investigation of the San Pedro River Basin, Southeastern Arizona, 1987 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Larson, Marvin and Scott- Report San Carlos Apache Farming Water Supply Alternatives, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Leonard Rice Consulting Water Engineers- Identification and Quantification of Water Right Entitlements and Diversions, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Leonard Rice Consulting Water Engineers- Methodology and Procedure for Identifying Subflow and Wells that Pump Subflow, 1993 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Manuscripts relating to Pima, Maricopa, Apaches, Casa Grande, 1926-1989 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Marr, James- The Use and Duty of Water in the Salt River Valley, 1927 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Master File abstract, undated (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Master File 000-00-00 to 862-11-263, undated (Box 98, Folder 17-18)
    - Master File 863-00-00 to 875-11-17, undated (Box 98, Folder 19-20)
    - Master File 876-00-00 to 883-12-31, undated (Box 98, Folder 21-22)
    - Master File 884-00-00 to 890-12-31, undated (Box 98, Folder 23-24)
    - Master File 891-00-00 to 902-06-30, undated (Box 99, Folder 1-2)
    - Master File 902-07-05 to 907-04-30, undated (Box 99, Folder 3-4)
    - Master File 907-05-00 to 911-08-24, undated (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
    - Master File 911-09-01 to 913-08-01, undated (Box 99, Folder 7-8)
    - Master File 913-08-01 to 917-07-31, undated (Box 99, Folder 9-10)
    - Master File 917-08-08 to 924-04-28, undated (Box 99, Folder 11-12)
    - Master File 924-05-01 to 927-12-31, undated (Box 99, Folder 13-14)
    - Master File 928-00-00 to 929-02-28.2, undated (Box 99, Folder 15-16)
    - Master File 929-03-04 to 931-05-29, undated (Box 100, Folder 1-2)
    - Master File 931-06-01 to 935-12-31.1, undated (Box 100, Folder 3-5)
    - Master File 936-00-00 to 938-04-30, undated (Box 100, Folder 6-8)
    - Master File 938-05-02 to 939-12-31, undated (Box 100, Folder 9-10)
    - Master File 940-00-00 to 941-07-28, undated (Box 100, Folder 11-12)
    - Master File 941-08-05 to 942-01-31.1, undated (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Master File 942-02-02 to 942-07-31, undated (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Master File 942-08-04 to 943-06-30, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Master File 943-07-01 to 947-06-26.1, undated (Box 101, Folder 2-4)
    - Master File 947-07-00 to 950-05-15, undated (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Master File 950-06-13 to 953-04-30, undated (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Master File 953-05-07 to 957-12-30, undated (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Master File 958-00-00 to 960-12-30.1, undated (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Master File 961-00-00 to 972-12-73, undated (Box 101, Folder 9-11)
    - Master File 973-00-00 to 994-11-03, undated (Box 101, Folder 12-13)
    - Master File 973-00-00 to 994-11-03, undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Matlock, Dutt and Strehlein- Salinity and Water Management in the Safford and Duncan- Virden Valleys, Arizona, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Meeting handouts, 1963-1994 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Meeting notes, 1963, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Meeting notes, 1983-1986 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Meeting notes, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Meeting notes, 1990-1997 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Meeting notes, 1998-2002 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Merchant, James- Economic Impacts from Changes in Irrigated Crop Production Upper Gila River Basin Arizona and New Mexico, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Mock, Peter- Technical Knowledge at the Time of the Globe Equity Decree No. 59, 2001 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Montgomery, Errol- Criteria for Determining Subflow, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Montgomery, Errol- General Hydrogeologic Conditions Lower San Pedro Basin Pinal County, Arizona, 1987 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Need for negotiation funding, 1986 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Nelson and Busch- Cost of Pumping Irrigation Water in Central, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Newell and Poitras- A Preliminary Analysis of the Arizona Department of Water Resources Adjudication Investigation System, 1992 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - News Clippings- The Advocate, 1905 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - News Clippings- Alta California, 1849-1876 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - News Clippings- Arivaca Briefs, 1954 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1900-1902 (Box 102, Folder 19)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1903-1904 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1905 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1907-1909 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1910-1911 (Box 102, Folder 23)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1912-1914 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1916-1917 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1918-1919 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1920 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1921-1922 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1923 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1924-1926 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1929-1933 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Blade- Tribune, 1934-1937 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Bulletin, 1898-1900 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Bulletin, 1901 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Bulletin, 1902-1905 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Bulletin, 1906-1907 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Bulletin, 1909 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Bulletin, 1910-1913 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Bulletin, 1914-1917 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Citizen, 1871-1891 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Daily Star, 1877-1880 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Daily Star, 1882-1899 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Daily Star, 1902-1919 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Daily Star, 1921-1935 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Daily Star, 1936-1958 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Daily Star, 1959-1965 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Daily Star, 1970-1999 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Enterprise, 1882-1888 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Enterprise, 1890-1891 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Gazette, 1884-1918 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings- Arizona newspapers, 1995-2000 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Republic, 1930-1983 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Republican, 1895-1904 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Republican, 1905-1906 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Republican, 1907-1910 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Republican, 1914-1919 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Republican, 1921-1965 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Republican Cotton Edition, 1919 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Sentinel, 1877 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Silver Belt, 1878-1881 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Silver Belt, 1884-1886 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Silver Belt, 1887-1889 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Silver Belt, 1891-1895 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings- Arizona Silver Belt, 1896-1970 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings- Arizonian, 1859, 1911 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- Benson News, 1922-1926 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Benson Signal, 1920 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Bisbee Daily Review, 1903- 1922 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Bisbee Daily Review, 1931, 1948 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- The Bulletin, 1913-1914 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- The Bulletin, 1918-1920 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- The Bulletin, 1921-1922 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings- The Bulletin, 1923-1924 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1914-1915 (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1916 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1917-1920 (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1921-1922 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1923-1924 (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1925 (Box 107, Folder 1-2)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1926-1927 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1928 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1929 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1930-1932 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1934 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1935 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1937-1938 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1939 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1940-1946 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1947-1949 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1950-1957 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1959-1963 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1969-1975 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1977-1980 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- The Coolidge News, 1928-1929 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Copper Era, 1904-1931 (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Douglas Daily Dispatch, 1916-1929 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Droughts, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- Florence Tribune, 1892-1898 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- Florence Tribune, 1889-1900 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1896-1897 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1922-1923 (Box 108, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1924-1925 (Box 108, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1926 (Box 108, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1927 (Box 108, Folder 14)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1928 (Box 108, Folder 15)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1929 (Box 108, Folder 16)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1930 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1931 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1932 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1933 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1934 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1935 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Graham County Guardian, 1939-1941 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- Mohave Miner, 1889-1895 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- The Oasis, 1894, 1900-1901 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- Phoenix Daily Herald, 1883 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - News Clippings- Phoenix Herald, 1882 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - News Clippings- Prescott Courier, 1866-1896 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - News Clippings- San Diego Union, 1874, 1916 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - News Clippings- San Francisco Herald, 1851 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - News Clippings- San Pedro Valley News, 1929-1945 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - News Clippings- San Pedro Valley News, 1947-1955 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - News Clippings- San Pedro Valley News, 1957-1958 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - News Clippings- San Pedro Valley News, 1963-1973 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings- San Pedro Valley News, 1974-1979 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings- San Pedro Valley News, 1981-1985 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings- San Pedro Valley News, 1986-1993 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings- Tombstone Daily Nugget, 1881 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings- Tombstone Epitaph, 1882-1923 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - News Clippings- Tucson Citizen, 1878-1979 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - News Clippings- The Valley Bulletin, 1889-1890 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings- Weekly Phoenix Herald, 1883 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - News Clippings- Yuma Sentinel, 1880-1881 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Newsletters, 1977-1990 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Newspaper Index, 1996 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Newspaper Index- Casa Grande Dispatch, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper Index- Casa Grande Times, 1913 (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper Index- Casa Grande Valley Dispatch, 1915 (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - No. 69 and 299 (Timber and Sawmill Claim), 1986 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - No. 88-1136-M, 1990 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - No. 90-168-11 and 90-16764- Pleadings, 1991 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - No. 236- Court Issued documents, 1981-1991 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - No. 236- D selected documents, 1969-1986 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - No. 236- D selected documents, 1985 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - No. 236- Deposition of Nicklason, Fred, 1983 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - No. 236- E selected documents, 1974-1978 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - No. 236 F and I, 1971-1986 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - No. 236- Indians Claims Commission documents, 1969-1985 (Box 111, Folder 5-6)
    - No. 236-N Accounting Report on: Reimbursable Loan for the Cotton Gin, 1917-1937 (Box 111, Folder 7-8)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1909 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1910 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1911 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1912 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1913 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1914 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1915 (Box 112, Folder 1-2)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1916 (Box 112, Folder 3-4)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1917 (Box 112, Folder 5-7)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1918 (Box 112, Folder 8-10)
    - No. 236- N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1921 (Box 112, Folder 11-12)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1922 (Box 112, Folder 13-14)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1924 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - No. 236-N Experimental Farm Disbursement Accounting, 1925 (Box 113, Folder 2-3)